个人翻译作品请勿用于商业用途 初次翻译诸多错误还望见谅
@嘉鱼鱼鱼鱼鱼鱼
谢谢 非常感谢
Thank you. Thanks very much.
女士们 先生们 今晚我带来了一位朋友
And ladies and gentlemen, I have a friend here tonight
和我一样 她离开家乡来到这
who like me, she's a long way from home.
如果他们不介意的话
And if it's ok with you.
我在想你们要不要让她唱首她的歌?
I was wondering if you'd like her to play one of her songs?
可以吗?好吗?
Is that okay? Yeah?
Gretta 能请你上来吗?
Gretta, will you come up here please?
稍等一下
Ahh, just give me a moment.
我觉得这会是个很好的主意
I think it'd be a really good idea
如果你能上来唱一首你的歌
if you'd come up here and sing one of your songs.
我认为这是一个很糟糕的主意
I think it'd be a really fucking bad idea.
- 来吧 Gretta 这可是纽约 - 不要!
- Gretta, come on. This is New York. - No!
你们都想听的 对吧?
You want to hear it, right?
你一定会超棒的
You're gonna be amazing.
嗨 这是一首新歌 所以可能会有点粗糙
Hi, ah, so this is a new song it might be kind of rough.
献给城市中所有寂寞的人们
It's for anyone who's ever been alone in the city.
A Step You Can't Take Back - Keira Knightley
你发现自己在地铁里
So you find yourself at this subway
当你的世界在包装下 随身携带
When your world in a bag by your side
一切似乎看起来很完美
And all at once it seemed like a good way
你意识到这就是你生命的终结
You realized its the end of your life
意义也就如此
For what it's worth
火车在轨道上奔驰而来
Here comes the train upon the track
带走伤痛只剩下一片黑
And there goes the pain it cuts to black
最后的行动你准备好了吗?
Are you ready for the last act?
踏上永不回头的征程
To take a step you can't take back
她爱你吗?
Did she love you?
她带给你伤痛吗?
Did she take you down?
在亲吻你的王冠时
Was she on her knees
她有没有双膝跪地?
when she kissed your crown?
告诉我你所知道的
Tell me what you found
大雨不期而至 抓紧你的帽子
Here comes the rain, so hold your hat
你发现自己在地铁里
So you find yourself at this subway
当你的世界在包装下 随身携带
When your world in a bag by your side
当天早些时候...
现在是早上7点 你好 纽约
It's 7AM. Good Moring, New York.
欢迎今早与Potsy和Andy的"第二小时"相会
And welcome to THE SECOND HOUR of Posty and Andy in the morning.
Potsy 你有听说过一只
Hey Potsy, did you read about a dog in
在一家韩国餐馆的狗的故事吗?
the Korean restaurant thing?
我当然听说过 你听说过吗 Katie?
Oh I certainly did. Did you hear about that, Katie?
潜力新人歌手 让我听听看都有些什么人
Fresh prospects, Let's hear it, what do you got for me?
不 不
No No!
下一个让谁来点亮这旅程?
Who's next on this delightful journey?
不 不 不 天 不行!完全不行!
No,no,no,no man! You can't! No! You can't!
这都什么破玩意儿
It's shit! It’s shit!
滚出我的车
Get fucking out of my car.
给我随便来点什么 一首歌 一点希望 什么都可以
Give me anything, a song, a hope anything I can work with...
我要求不高
I'm not asking for much...
这还行 还可以
That's something, that's good.
如果你不再唱了的话
Until you started to sing!
妈妈在哪?
Where's mom?
我女儿在哪呢?
Where's my daughter?
你什么意思?
What do you mean?
你妈今天要截稿 她让我今天来照顾你
Your mom has a deadline, she asked me to watch you today.
上车吧
Let's go.
好了 你现在想要去哪?自然历史博物馆吗?
So where do you want to go? The Museum of Natural History?
或者是去公园吃个冰淇淋还是怎样?
You want to go to the park and get some ice cream, or what?
我为什么要干那些?我又不是小孩子
Why would I want to do that? I'm not a kid.
车上什么味道?
What's that smell?
哦 是汽油味 我在加满油的时候
Oh that's gasoline. I was filling up the car with gasoline
我洒了点在我裤子上
and I spilled a little on my pant leg.
并不是酒
That isn't alcohol.
我感觉我好像要在这开个会
I think I've got a meeting here.
你要在这里等还是要一起进去?
You want to wait here or you want to come with me?
你感觉你有个会?你到底有没有?
You think you have a meeting? Do you or not?
去看看呗
Let's see.
看 这很不错吧
See, this is fun, right?
我们第一次来这附近的时候还是在92年
When we came into this neighborhood in 92.
那时这里一个人也没有 就像一个战区
There was nobody here, it was like a war-zone.
都是妓女啊 盗贼啊 现在高雅多了
Hookers. Crack. Now it's totally gentrified.
我知道的 老爸
I know, Dad.
- 我来过的 - 那好 现在我们要上去了 尽量保持安静
- I've had the tour. - Okay we're going to go up there. Just be quiet.
我认为这是公司赚取利润的一个好方法
I think it's a great way to generate revenue for the company.
- 你来啦 交通很糟糕么? - 没有 交通很通畅啊 我只是路过一下
- Hey.Hmm,was there bad traffic? - No,traffic was actually pretty good. I was just passing by.
我们刚结束音频评论会
We were just hmm...closing up about the audio commentary piece.
恩 太糟糕了
Yeah, shit idea.
这是个糟糕的想法 怎么讨论也是糟糕的
It was a shit idea then, Still a shit idea. It didn't age well.
我们感谢你的坦率
We appreciate your candor.
但是今天我们涌现了很多不同的意见
But we had a different view of it here though.
我是说 现在大多数的音乐家是
I mean. Musicians for the most part are pretty much...
十几岁没什么话好说的青少年
Monosyllabic teenagers who really don't have much to say...
这想法不错吧
and that's the good one, right?
这样的话我们还在这里做什么?
So what are we doing here?
音乐行业好着呢 会一直好下去的
The music industry is fine. It's always gonna be fine.
我们现在很稳定
We always have been fine.
也许孩子们说的是对的 也许音乐真的应该免费
Maybe the kids are right. Maybe music should be free anyway.
从唱片公司老板听到这番话可真可怕
That's an alarming thing to hear the head of a record company say.
怕什么?真相么?
What? The truth?
谢谢你 Karen我们回聊感谢你的到来
Well,hmm...Thanks so much, Karen. Let's talk more. We really appreciate it.
是的 当然
Yeah, of course.
很高兴认识你
Great meeting you.
我很高兴大家都能理解这个问题
I'm glad we got it all figured out.
乐队评论他们自己音乐的音轨
The band doing audio commentary on their own music.
这是唯一套路 Saul 你是知道的
It's so fucking lame, Saul, you know it!
如果是十年前的话 你肯定会看不起那些主意的
10 years ago, man, you would have shit on that idea.
这也是一些东西 一些想法
It's something, it's an idea.
这些想法说不定能打开思路 这都是些东西
It's something that helps keep the lights on. It's something.
我们需要创造力 而不是什么噱头 这就是我们
We need vision, not gimmicks.That's us.
我一直在跟你做 Mulligan先生
I've been following you, Mr.Mulligan
寻找各种有潜力的人
Down a track on every long shot.
然后带到这里 但在过去的5年里
You've been bringing in here the last five years.
他们之中有人红了么?
And which one of them has come in.
有么?
Which one?
Dan Dan.
Dan Dan
再见 Saul
See you later, brother Saul.
Dan.
Dan
我们需要谈谈
We need to talk, man.
回来 你别走 你不能这么做
Come back here. Don't you walk away from me.You can't do this shit, man.
你不能这么做
You can't pull this shit, dude.
你不能这样对我
You can't pull this shit.
不要这样
Don't do this here.
我就要这么做
I'm going to do it right fucking here.
好的 那我就这么做了
All right, then let's do it then!
因为他们知道 这些人知道
Because they know. These people know
他们能够在这上班
that they are sitting behind those desks
是因为我建立了一个独立的唱片公司
is because I started an independent record label.
在那家酒吧开始的 Saul
Above that bar, Saul.
我们已经改变了当时做事的方式
And we changed the way things are going to be done, man.
培育然后培养
Nurture and foster.
一切都变了 时代变了
Things change. Times change.
人们必须做出改变 Dan
People gotta change with them, Dan.
这样已经没用了
It's not working.
你得走了
You gotta go.
我可没时间浪费在这
I don't have time for this.
我还有自己的事要处理 好吗?
I've got my own shit going on, all right?
我要去拿我的客户名单了
I'm taking my client list.
我要走了 我他妈的这就走
I'm out of here, man. I am fucking out of here.
你在说什么 他们已经和我们签署了合同
What are you talking about? They signed to us.
不要打扰她 别打扰她
Don't bother her. Don't bother her.
她可不会什么事都替你做
That's not Jerry McGuire.
走吧 爸爸
Dad, let's go.
那我要带走我的画 就这么决定了 我要带走我的画
I'm taking my art then. That's it. I'm taking the art.
这是我的画 我花的钱 是我买的 是我选的
It's my art. I paid for it. I bought it. I picked it out.
- 没问题 没问题 我拿着呢 - 你想去哪?
- I got this. I got it. I got it. - Where are you going?
好吧 先放这里
Okay. Leave it there.
我会回来拿的 这是我的
I'm coming back for that.It's mine.
所有的东西都是我的
All of that is mine.
走吧 宝贝
Come on, baby.
你想要再喝一杯吗?
You want another one?
恩 我想 但我不会要的 不行 我不能
Ah, I do but I won't. I mustn't. I can't.
他怎么能炒掉我 是我建立了那个公司诶!
How could he fire me when I set the whole fucking thing up?
是你么?
Did you?
你怎么一点也不了解你爸我
Don't you know anything about your father?
不 我知道
Yeah I do.
妈妈经常说的
I know what mom says.
你妈妈说什么?
What does mom say?
她说你只是个悲惨的失败者
She says you're a pathetic loser.
她说得真亲切
She says that affectionately.
你呢?
What about you?
你怎么觉得?
What do you think?
我不怎么了解你
I don't really know you.
你知道两年的时间对一个十几岁的孩子来说是很长的
You know two years is a long time in the life of a teenager.
你这说话方式哪学的?
Where did you learn to talk like that?
我的心理医生
My psychiatrist.
心理医生?你有心理医生?
Psychiatrist? You have a psychiatrist now?
是的 妈妈觉得这挺好的
I do. Mom thought it'd be a good idea.
我有点行为怪异
I was acting strange.
你没什么奇怪的 你只是个15岁的青少年
There's nothing strange about you.You're 15 years old.
你并不需要什么心理医生
You don't need a fucking psychiatrist.
相信我 我知道的 我比任何人都了解你
Believe me, I know. I know you better than anybody.
恩 当然了 爸爸
Yeah, you sure do, dad.
你说我几岁来着?
How old did you say I was?
我刚说15岁?
Did I say you were 15?
我是指 是指14岁
I meant you were 14.
我刚说15吗?
Did I say 15?
你有还酒的钱么?
You got money to pay for these beers?
我是个孩子 我哪来的钱?
I'm a kid. I don't have any money on me!
你的零花钱呢?
What happened to your pocket money?
我拿去买避孕套了
Well, I spent that on condoms.
什么?不 不 不 不 不
What? No, no, no, no, no.
信息量太大了
Too much information.
你准备好了吗?干嘛?
You ready?For what?
- 有趣的是吧 是吧?不要笑 - 恩 是挺有趣的 老爸
That was fun, right? Don't smile.It was fun, dad.
是啊 好久没这么开心了
Yeah. You had a good time.
你还小的时候我们都没这样过 真是有趣
We haven't run like that since we were little. That was good.
他是你爸么?
Is he your daddy?
我很高兴你在这里因为我正准备上车...
I'm glad you're here because I was just going to the car...
你还好吗?我很好
Are you okay?I'm fine.
对不起 是我的错 祝你有个愉快的一天
I'm sorry, my bad. Have a great day.
我还是能够打败他的 会让他出丑的
I could have taken that guy. He still had to make a scene.
帮我件事 好吗?不要告诉妈妈我今天被炒了 听着
Do me a favor, all right? Don't tell your mom I lost my job today.Listen to me.
感谢你让我度过了极其平常的一天
Thanks for a really normal day, dad.
什么?
What?
大家好啊
Hello, everyone.
- 嗨
- Hi.
工作怎样?
How's work?
还行
Fine.
你饿了吧
You look hungry.
老师真的很担心她
Her teachers are really worried about her.
没有女孩子喜欢她 她很难接近
No girls like her at school. She is distant.
想跟她玩的
And the only people who want to hang out with her
都是那些想和她睡的大男孩
are older boys who want to fuck her.
哦 是这样吗?我并不感到惊讶
Oh really? And you find that a big surprise.
你让她穿着就像
You let her walk out of the house looking like...
Jodie Foster在"出租车司机"里一样走出家门?
like Jodie Foster from "Taxi Driver"?
她有自己想要的穿衣方式
She dresses the way she wants to.
- 而且如果女儿穿成那样只是想要一件事 - 当皮条客?
- And any daughter who dresses like that only wants one thing. - A pimp?
不 Dan 想想吧
No, Dan. Think about it.
这都是瞎扯!她需要些教育 天啊
That is fucking bullshit.She needs some guidance for fucking sake.
你走进来就跟个小丑似的
You walks in here like a fucking clown.
还对我教育孩子指手画脚
You tell me how to raise my kid.
你只不过是一个月来接孩子出去一次
The kid that you pick up once a month.
就说得你很有良心似的
And decide you have a fucking conscience about.
你知道吗?你离开这里30秒后
You know what? Thirty seconds after you're gone.
我们就完全忘记了你曾经在这里
We'll have totally forgotten you were ever here.
谢谢
Thank you.
我以为我没希望了
I thought there was no hope.
我以为已经没有答案了
I thought there were no answers.
但是后来我遇见了上帝
And then I found God.
他也许不会一直在我们身边
God may not always be on our time.
但他总会准时到来
But he's on time.
我们永远不会孤单
We're never alone.
先生?去吧 跟上帝谈谈吧
Sir? Go, have a talk with God.
好的 很好
Right, Man. OK.
我会跟他谈谈的 好么?
I'm gonna have a little talk with God, all right?
谢谢
Thank you.
如果他不回答呢?
What if he doesn't answer?
请注意由于Jay Street站的出现故障
Attention. Due to a signal malfunction at Jay Street
下一班列车将在20分钟后抵达
the next uptown train will arrive in 20 minutes.
快来一杯波旁酒
Give me a bourbon. Hurry up.
你想要哪种?
What kind of bourbon you want?
随便
I don't care.
我在想能不能让她上来唱首歌
and I was wondering if it'd be okay if she sang a song.
好吗?可以吗?Gretta 能请你上来吗?
Is that okay? Yeah? Gretta, would you come up here please?
嗨 这是一首新歌 还不是很完美
So this is a new song so it might be kind of rough.
献给城市中所有寂寞的人们
It's for anyone who's ever been alone in the city.
你发现自己在地铁里
So you find yourself at this subway
当你的世界在包装下 随身携带
When your world in a bag by your side
一切似乎看起来很完美
And all at once it seemed like a good way
你意识到这就是你生命的终结
You realized its the end of your life
意义也就如此
For what it's worth
火车在轨道上奔驰而来
Here comes the train upon the track
带走伤痛只剩下一片黑
And there goes the pain it cuts to black
最后的行动你准备好了吗?
Are you ready for the last act?
踏上永不回头的征程
To take a step you can't take back
承受所有你能承受的逆境
Take in all the punches you could take
把一切放进心里
Took 'em all right on your chest
此刻 无数次的回头打破这一切
Now the countless back is breaking
再一次 再一次
Again, again
意义也就如此
For what it's worth
火车在轨道上奔驰而来
Here comes the train upon the track
带走伤痛
And there goes the pain
只剩下一片黑
it cuts to black
最后的行动你准备好了吗
Are you ready for the last act?
踏上
To take a step
永不回头的征程
you can't take back
她爱你吗?
Did she love you?
她带给你伤痛吗?
Did she take you down?
在亲吻你的王冠时
Was she on her knees
她有没有双膝跪地?
when she kissed your crown?
告诉我你所知道的
Tell me what you found
大雨不期而至 抓紧你的帽子
Here comes the rain, so hold your hat
不要祈祷上帝 因为他不会跟你对讲
And don't pray to God, cause He won't talk back
最后的行动你准备好了吗?
Are you ready for the last act?
踏上永不回头的征程
To take a step you can't take back
不回头 不回头
Back, back
你不会回头
You can't take back
不回头 不回头
Back, back
你发现自己在地铁里
So you find yourself at this subway
当你的世界在包装下 随身携带
with your world in a bag by your side
- 我要加入 - 什么?
- I'm in. - What?
我想帮你出唱片 我想当你的制作人
I want to make records with you，I want to produce you.
我想要签你 我们注定要一起合作
I want to sign you. We're meant to work together.
对不起 你没看见他们的反应么?
Sorry, didn't you just see what happened up there?
看见了啊 那又怎样 你觉得不好么?
Yeah, what? Are you feeling sorry for yourself?
不 我喜欢我的音乐 反正他们也不懂是吧?
No, I like my music. I mean who cares if they don't get it, right?
你只需要稍微改善一下你的表演形式
You just need to work on your performance a little bit.
我不是表演家 我只是偶尔写点歌
I'm not a performer. I just write songs from time to time.
其他歌也跟这首一样好么?
And are those songs as good as that one?
你真是个制作人?
Are you really an A and R man?
但你看起来就像个无家可归的人
You just look more like a homeless man.
我只是出来庆祝一下
I've been out celebrating all week.
我刚刚签了一个新乐队 我们感到非常兴奋
And I just signed a band and we got carried away.
你刚才唱的这首歌
That's some song you've got there.
我敢保证一定会大热 你又这么漂亮
I promise you it could be a big hit. Plus you're beautiful.
等等 这跟长相又有什么关系?
Sorry, what does beauty got to do with anything?
天啊 你还挺精明的是吧?
Jesus, you’re tricky aren't you?
不 我是觉得是音乐是用耳朵来听的 而不是用眼睛看
No, I actually just think that music is about ears not eyes.
而且我不是从灰狗巴士上走下来的Judy Garland
And I'm not Judy Garland just off a Greyhound bus.
想要寻找新开始 不过说真的 还是谢谢你
looking for stardom, but really, thank you.
- 好吧 再见 - 再见
- Okay, bye. - Bye.
所以 在你走之前
So before you go
享受我的表演
Enjoy my show
- 好吧 其实事实是这样的 我想签你我也做不到 好吗? - 好吧
- OK, here's the truth. I couldn't have signed you if I wanted to, alright? - OK.
我今晚来着并不是想要签谁
I didn't come from a signing tonight.
我已经七年没跟人签过合同了
I haven't signed anybody in seven years.
我的公司已经对我完全失去信心了
My label has completely lost all faith in me.
那你为什么还给我你的名片?
So why did you give me your card?
职业病罢了 我看起来像无家可归的人么 事实上是可以这么说
Force of habit.If I look homeless it's because I practically am.
我离开家大约有一年了
I left my home about a year or so ago.
我住在一个地毯皱巴巴的糟糕的公寓里
I'm sleeping on a shitty mattress in some shitty apartment.
今晚来这也不是来庆祝的
And I wasn't celebrating tonight.
我醉醺醺地站在铁轨旁 准备自杀
I was drinking my ass off standing on a subway platform ready to kill myself.
然后 我听见了你的歌
And then I heard your song.
- 想要喝杯酒吗? - 好啊 - 走
- Want to get a beer? - Sure. - Yeah, come on.
"Dan Mulligan 生于1966年
Dan Mulligan. Born 1966
在海岛唱片公司工作两年
Headed A&R department at Island Records for two years
之后与哈佛友人Saul Byron
Left to co-found indie label Distressed Records
共同创立独立音乐厂牌"
with Harvard classmate, Saul Byron."
所以 你有自己的厂牌?
So, you own Distressed Records?
但因为感情问题 我卖出了我所有的股权
I sold all my interest due to emotional difficulties.
什么感情问题?
What emotional difficulties?
我太情绪化了而已 继续读下去
I was too emotional. Read on.
"90年代初 纽约开始流行起hip-pop音乐
"Very active on the hip-hop scene in New York in the early 90s
他挖掘了
the pair were responsible for discovering
许多创作型的歌手并获得两项格莱美奖
numerous break-through artists on two Grammys as producer.
现与他的女儿以及妻子--音乐记者Miriam Hart一起居住在纽约
Lives in New York with wife--music journalist Miriam Hart, and their daughter.
格莱美奖是怎么回事?
What happened to the Grammys?
我把奖杯都当掉了
I pawned them.
你当掉?赚了多少?
You pawned them? How much did you get for them?
两个奖杯共一百二十五美元
A hundred and twenty five for the both of them.
导致我前几个月一直醉着酒
Which got me wasted one weekend a couple months ago.
听我的歌时你也是醉着的吗?
Were you drunk when you heard my song?
当然 这样才能创造奇迹
Absolutely, babe. That's when the magic happens.
- 什么奇迹? - 我从你的歌里听出一些东西
- What magic? - I hear things.
一些东西?
You hear things?
编曲 也许得醉了才能听的出来
Arrangements. Maybe need to be drunk for that sort of thing.
那你真是太醉了
You must have been drunk tonight.
因为在哪都能听到些东西
because nobody else heard anything.
不 你的歌真的很棒 就是你的感觉
No, your song's good. It's you.
站在那里就像个假小子
Standing up there like a tomboy.
无意冒犯
I don’t mean to be offensive...
- 但你不觉得这样看着有点消极? - 真的吗?
- But don't you think that looks a little pass? - Really?
说真的 我们能把你包装好
Seriously. We get you a look.
再配上超品质的音乐视频 你一定能大热
And a killer video. And you'll go straight to the top.
我想到诺拉 琼斯 各种创作型歌手...
I’m thinking Nora Jones. Singer songwriter thing...
钢琴乐队还有羊毛衫合唱团
and The Piano or The Cardigans.
想想他们刚到美国的样子吧 或者说像黛博拉 哈瑞一样
Back in the day when they first came to America. Maybe even Deborah Harry.
给你后面配上乐队 怎么了?你觉得这很好笑?
A male band behind you，What? You find that amusing?
不 对不起 但好像有什么不对劲
No, I'm sorry. Something went down the wrong way.
你在把我跟羊毛衫合唱团还有诺拉 琼斯放在一个段位上?
No, you were saying? Me with a Cardigan on? Nora Jones?
那你觉得自己是什么水平?
Babe, what the fuck do you think you are?
怎么?你以为你就拿着一把吉他站在舞台上
What? You gonna stand up on a stage with a beat-up guitar
就会成为新一代卡洛儿 金?
and you think you're the new Carole-fucking-King?
不 我只是觉得一个制作人告诉一个歌手如何穿着
No. I just think that an A&R man telling an artist how they should dress
如何给人印象简直是瞎扯
or come across is total bullshit.
观众也不希望看到那些花哨的 他们想要的是真实
People don't want that，They want authenticity.
行 你要真实是吧
Okay, babe. Authenticity.
给我一个音乐人你认为是能通过你的真实测试
Give me the name of one artist that you think passes your authenticity test.
- 迪伦 - 迪伦 他是你能想到的最真实的艺术家?
- Dylan. - Dylan. That is the most cultivated artist you could have thought of?
看看他的头发 他的墨镜 甚至他的脸都会十年变一次
Look at his hair. His sunglasses. He changes his look every decade.
兰迪 纽曼
Randy Newman.
我真的很喜欢兰迪 纽曼 好吧 那算你赢了
I fucking love Randy Newman. Okay, you got me on that.
听着
Listen to me.
我并不是说你不能
I am not saying that you can't be
达到这个行业的顶端
a real bona fide motherfucker in this business.
但是你要不惜一切代价
But you got to do whatever it takes
让人们看你表演
and get people in to see your shows
让你的音乐搞出一番大事业来
where the music can start to do its real work.
天啊 我们到底在讨论些什么
Oh my God. What were we even talking about?
你又不能签我 我也不想被签
You can't sign me. And I don't want to be signed.
就是这样!为什么不喜欢被签呢?
Thats right. What's not to like?
来 走吧
Come on, let' get out of here.
糟糕 不过你得付一下酒钱
Ah, shit. You're gonna have to get these beers, though.
好吧 那很高兴认识你
OK. So it was really nice to meet you.
你要去哪?
Where you going?
回去睡觉啊 明天还要赶飞机
To sleep. I have a plane to catch tomorrow.
去哪?
Where?
- 家 - 为什么?
- Home. - Why?
我已经厌倦这座城市了 我想要回大学了
Because I'm sick of this city and I want to go back to Uni.
拜托 没有人会就这样来到纽约
Oh, come on. No one comes to New York
然后什么都不做就离开了
and just leaves without something terrible happening.
怎么了?发生了什么事情?
What? What happened to you?
来吧 来跟我说说吧 我又不是什么悲惨的陌生人
Come on. You can share with me. I' m no stranger to misery.
你就来我们公司录个样本给我合伙人听听
Just come to my label and let me play your demo to my partner.
如果行不通的话
If it doesn't work out.
就让我来付改签机票的钱
I will personally pay to change your ticket.
为何不在纽约多呆一天放声大哭?
What's one more day in New York for crying out loud?
反正你回家了也是闷闷不乐的
You're just probably gonna go home and mope around anyway.
好吧 好吧
All right. All right.
我回家考虑一下
I'm gonna go home and think about it.
我明早再打电话给你
And, I'll call you either way tomorrow.
行么?
OK?
- 赞 - 是啊
- Good answer. - Yeah.
- 非常高兴认识你 - 我也是
- It was very nice to meet you. - Yes, pleasure.
是我的荣幸
Pleasure's mine.
- 你有我电话的吧? - 有
- You've got my number, right? - Yeah.
Lost Stars - Keira Knightley
Please don't see
请不要嘲笑
Just a girl caught up in dreams
这只不过是一个沉浸在梦
and fantasies
与幻想中的女孩
Please see me reaching out
好好看看我吧
for someone I can see
伸出双臂去拥抱那些看不见的人
Take my hand let's see
牵着我的手
where we wake up tomorrow
看看明天我们会在哪里醒来
Best laid plans sometimes
缜密的计划有时
it's just a one night stand
莫过于一夜的陪伴
I'd be damned Cupid's demanding
爱已消失
back his arrow
我已心碎
嗨 是Dave么?
Hi, Dave?
嗨 我是Jill 我是唱片公司的接待员
Hi, I'm Jill. I work in hospitality with the label.
- 很高兴认识你 - 我也是
- Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you, too.
你好 很高兴认识你
Hi, nice to meet you.
我来拿吧 跟我来这边 谢谢你 Marco
Got it. Right this way. Thank you, Marco.
我觉得你们会很喜欢这所公寓 非常高档
I think you're really gonna like the apartment. It's very high end.
- 抱歉 你是Dave Kohl吗? - 是的
- I'm sorry. Are you emm...You're Dave Kohl. - Yes.
你看!我说是的吧!
Yeah. I told you guys!
我们几天前看了你的电影 很喜欢你的那首歌
We saw your film the other day. I so love your songs in it.
谢谢 这是我女朋友Gretta 她也写歌
Thank you. This is Gretta, my girlfriend. She writes songs too.
真好!请问能帮我们拍张照么 棒极了 按一下这个键就好
Ah, cool! Would you mind taking our photograph? That'd be so awesome. Just that button right there.
- 好了 很不错 - 谢谢
- Yeah, it's a good one. - Thank you.
恐怕你得慢慢习惯起来了
You're gonna have to get used to that, I'm afraid.
这部电影在纽约都卖光了 太疯狂了
This movie is selling out all over town. It's pretty crazy.
- 真是难以置信 - 不 这可是真的
- Unbelievable. - Oh, no. It's real.
好啦 就是这儿啦
All right, here we are.
希望你们会喜欢
We hope you like.
冰箱里面吃的也已经买好了
Your fridge in here is stocked with food.
桌上有两串钥匙
There are two sets of keys on the table in there.
这上面有司机的号码还有我的 我就放在这
This is your driver's number and my cell phone number.I'll leave that here.
你们中午要来公司和大家见个面
You're due at the label later this afternoon to meet everyone.
然后我们会带你们在工作室里转转
And then we'll take a tour around the studio.
你们也许想睡一会儿
So, probably want to catch up on your sleep before then.
我就先走了好么?
I'll leave you to it. Okay?
- 很高兴认识你 Gretta - 我也是
- Pleased to meet you, Gretta. - Me too.
这地方挺一般的
This place is a shithole.
- 我能问你件事么 - 当然
- Hey. Can I ask you something? - Sure.
我要不要先离开一两个星期
Should I have come over in a week or two
让你自己好好适应这里?
and let you settle in first and get used to everything?
- 不要 - 你确定吗? - 是啊 没有你我什么都做不了 这里挺可怕的
- No. - Are you sure? - Yeah. I don't know if I could do this without you. It's kind of scary.
我这么说会不会太娘炮?
Am I a wimp for saying that?
你们来啦
Hey, there he is.
嗨 Dave 你好么
Big Dave. What's up, kid?
很高兴见到你 Gretta
Good to see you. Gretta.
来吧 进来吧
Come on in, guys.
让Dave坐在最前面
Put Dave at the head of the table.
太棒了
All right. I like it.
- 你们和大家见过了么? - 大家好
- You guys meet everyone? - Hi everybody.
这位是我的助手Mim 很漂亮吧
My assistant, Mim. The beautiful Mim.
这位是市场部的Milred
This is Mildred from Marketing.
还有媒体营销的Billy
Billy there is Social Media.
团队里剩下的人以后你们都会接触到的
The rest of the gang, you'll meet, spend time with.
那么 Gretta你也能在乐队里弹一两首歌吧?
So, Gretta you're gonna play guitar on a track or two, I hope, right?
- 可以的 如果Dave想要的话 - 是的
- Oh yeah, sure. If Dave wants. - Yeah.
这些年来Gretta一直在我一起做音乐
Gretta and I have been writing together for a couple years now.
甚至到这电影完成之前.
Even before the film came along.
我也很乐意去尝试表演些她的歌
So, I would love for us to try a couple of her songs.
你也参与了这次音乐电影的歌曲编写吗?
Did you write on the film with him?
不 没有
No, no.
是我们在电影拍完后写的那首 对吧?Dave?
That's the sound we're after is from the movie, right? Dave?
- 是的 - 是吗?对吗?没错? - 对 没错
- Of course. - Oui? Si? Capice? - Yes
Gretta给我提供了许多灵感
Gretta is very much apart of the inspiration behind everything.
她不仅仅是我的女友
She's not just my girlfriend.
她确实也是我的一部分
I just wanted to include her.
说白了 我只是一直跟随着他
Just to be completely clear. I'm just tagging along on this.
我很高兴能来这儿
I'm really happy to be here.
更开心能和Dave一起工作
And happy to accompany Daveon a couple of tracks.
这姑娘嘴真甜 是吧 我喜欢
How sweet is this girl? I love that.
这两人真棒!我爱他们
How great are these guys? I love them.
No One Else Like You - Adam Levine
是的 我会继续巡演乐队
Yeah, I'm going on tour with the band.
滚石杂志
Rolling Stone.
是啊 谢谢了 聊得很开心 谢谢
Yeah. Thank you so much. It was great talking to you. Thanks.
这是什么东西?
What's that?
- 是抹茶 - 抹茶? - 是啊
- That's matcha tea. - Matcha tea? - Yeah.
它含有大约400万的抗氧化物质
It's got like four million antioxidants in it.
- 我的天 喝起来像尿 - 那是我喜欢的
- Oh my God, it tastes like piss. - I like it.
武士去打战前都会喝抹茶
The samurais used to drink it before they went into battle.
你又不是武士 你是一个音乐人
You're not a samurai. You're a songwriter.
但我也很喜欢武士
Well, I'm kind of like a samurai.
是吗?
Are you?
我要把这拿去给他们了
I'm gonna give these to the guys.
- 我们星期一要去洛杉矶一个星期 - 我们要去洛杉矶?
- Oh, hey. We gotta go to LA for a week on Monday. - We're going to LA?
不 抱歉 是我和公司的人 他们在那有办公室
No. Sorry. It's just with some of the label guys. They have an office out there.
他们想让我见见视频导演
They want me to meet this video director guy.
还有我很想让你听听这个 好吗?
But, in the meantime, I'd really like you to listen to this. So, yes?
好的 对不起 我先去送咖啡
Yes, I'm sorry. I'll deliver coffee.
伙计们 我们再来一次好吗?
Hey guys, can we do this again, please?
第二次 开始
Take two. And rolling.
No One Else Like You - Adam Levine
一切都刚刚好吗?
Is everything just right?
不想让你觉得我太赶时间
Don't want you thinking that I'm in a hurry
我并不会害怕
I won't stay afraid
我有着让我担心的愿景
I had this vision that has got me worried
因为每个人都想要某个人
'Cause everyone wants someone
这些陈词滥调都是真的
That's one cliché that's true
除了你我真的谁都不想要
Except you I want no one
除非那个人还是你
Unless that someone's you
看你来像你 感觉起来还是你
It looks like you. Feels like you
笑起来像你 我希望那个人像你一样
Smiles like you. I want someone just like you
真诚而且永远那么清纯
True and through Forever blue
因为没有人像你一样
'Cause there's no one else like
谢谢
Thank you.
看看是谁!
Look at you!
这三个月他一直呆在工作室
He has the studio for three months.
然后我们会去巡演 所以 我们估计要呆个半年
And then we go on tour. So I think we're staying for six?
真是不敢相信 你简直就像是一个摇滚明星
This is unbelievable. You're total rock stars.
- 哪个唱片公司和他在合作? - Electric lady
Which studio is he working with? Electric lady.
- 卧槽啊! - 很酷是吧? - 你在开玩笑吗
- Oh fuck off! - It's really cool, isn't it? - Are you serious?
这是我的房间
So this is me.
- 这很棒啊 - 是啊 就像老笑话讲的一样
- Oh, this is lovely. - Yeah, it's like that old joke.
有开门的钥匙却还是要破窗进来
You put the key in the door,you break a window.
我的天 看看你的这些东西
My god, look at all this stuff.
是的 有很多工作室正在升级
Yeah, a lot of the studios are upgrading.
- 都不要这些东西了 我都可以靠这些录一张专辑了 - 那很酷诶
- So practically giving stuff away. I can record an album here soon. - Well, that'd be cool.
你的CD成堆了
Look at you, you've got CDs.
是啊 我刚把我所有的磁带扔掉了 坐在这儿吧
Yeah. I just phased out all my cassettes. Sit down.
你真是很怀旧啊
How retro of you.
你要威士忌还是水?
I have whiskey. Or water?
威士忌!
Whiskey, please!
就知道你
Of course you will.
看看你都有什么
Look what you've got.
这里的人都为这张专辑疯狂了
People are going crazy for that here.
当我表演的时候大家知道
When I play a show and the people know
当我去布里斯托尔大学之后 他们问的第一件事就是认不认识你的男朋友
I went to college in Bristol. The first thing they ask is if I know your boyfriend.
可不是吗?我回家后就成了"Dave Kohl的女朋友"
Yeah, tell me about it. I'm becoming "Dave Kohl's girlfriend" back home.
然后我就想说"我们本来是个团队的 到底发生了什么?"
I'm like, "Hello, we used to be a team. What happened?"
你知道吗?他们把你的歌放到电影里去了
Oh, you know what they say. Get your songs in a movie.
- 然后 这就是我的全部了 天知道我这样过了多久 - 我喜欢
- So, this is me. This is where I've been for God knows how long. - I love that.
- 是吗? - 是啊 - 你看见那张床了么?这是我自己做的 是我的床
- Do you? - Yeah. - Did you see the bed? I made that bed. That bed is mine.
- 太厉害了 你怎么爬上去的? - 跳上去呗
- That's very impressive. How'd you get up there? - I vault.
撑个杆子跳上去吗?
You vault? With a pole?
不用杆子 我用滑板的 一个滑板就行
No, no pole. I do it in one straight...one straight luge.
除非我喝醉了 那我就掉下来了
Unless I'm drunk. In which case. It's off on a dismount.
我喜欢这张专辑的背面 他拿吉他的方式
It's the back I like. It's like he's holding a guitar.
但他想让你觉得这是他老二
But he wants you to think it's his penis.
他说"看 这是一把吉他
He's saying, Look, it's a guitar.
但并不是这样 这是我老二的实际尺寸"
But it's not. This is the actual size of my penis.
为什么不呢?
Why, no?
因为必须要让你发挥一下 以同样的方式 让你也玩一玩
I am gonna shoot this because you have to play thatexactly the way you just played it.
好了 那你来弹吉他
Okay, you play the guitar.
因为没伴奏我可唱不起来
Because I can't do that when that thing's on.
- 是G调哦 - 我知道是G - 我不喜欢G
- It's in G. - I know G. - I don't like G.
没关系 你知道吗?你必须克服它
It doesn't matter. And you know what? You have to get over this.
这是一次锻炼
This is an exercise.
好的 准备好了吗?
Yes. Ready?
慢一点
Slower.
Please don't see.
这只不过是
Just a girl caught up in dreams and fantasies.
一个小女孩坐观空仰梦幻
Please see me
我要用心
reaching out for someone I can't see.
触碰身边的意中人
Take my hand.
牵起我的手吧
Let's see where we wake up tomorrow.
看看明天我们会梦醒何处
Best laid plans
也别再计划了
sometimes are just a one night stand.
等待一夜就知心属
I'll be damned
就让丘比特
cupid's demanding back his arrow.
收回那犹豫不决的箭吧
So let's get drunk on our tears.
就让我们饮醉在那压抑的泪水中吧
And god, tell us the reason.
上帝请告诉我们
Youth is wasted on the young.
年轻并非是虚度青春的理由
It's hunting season
又到了这追逐的季节
and the lambs are on the run
羔羊们都在纵情跳跃
searching for meaning.
找寻着生命的意义
But are we all lost stars
若夜空中星辰不再相互凝望闪烁
trying to light up the dark?
将如何继续照亮黑暗
好了 觉得怎么样?
Done. What'd you think?
我怎么觉得?
What do I think?
我觉得我现在很生气 实在太赞了 让我想生你的气了
I think I'm angry. I think I'm mad at you because it's so good
甚至可能还有点恨你了
that I hate you a little bit.
真的很赞!
So incredible good!
- 真的吗? - 是啊 - 真的吗? - 是啊 歌名是什么?
- Yeah? - Yeah. - Really? - Yeah. What's it called?
我不知道 "Lost stars"?你喜欢这个名字么?
I don't know. "Lost Stars"? You like it?
我不仅是喜欢 我觉得我太爱这首歌了 然后我觉得这太厉害了!
I don't like it. I think it's I love it. And I think it's incredible.
所以这歌是关于我么?不是写给你其他的男朋友 对吧?
And is it? is it about me? Or, it's not about your other boyfriend, right?
我不知道它是不是关于你 但绝对是为你写的
I don't know if it's about you.But it's definitely for you.
- 那我收下了 - 其实这是你的圣诞礼物因为我买不起别的
- I'll take it. - It is actually your Christmas present 'cause I can't afford to buy you another one
- 所以圣诞快乐! - 这是我唯一想要的圣诞礼物 圣诞快乐
- so happy Christmas! - This is the only Christmas present I want. Happy Christmas.
- 谢谢你 - 我爱你 - 我爱你
- Thank you very much. - I love you. - I love you.
快关掉!快关掉!
Turn it off. Turn it off.
- 我好想你 - 我也是 - 你都做了什么?
- I missed you. - I missed you. - What did you do?
也没什么事 就是到处闲逛
Nothing, really. I just kind of hung around here.
- 我去了几个植物园 - 真的吗? - 都非常有趣
- And I went to some botanical gardens. - Oh really? - It was very lovely.
那很棒
It was good.
- 我写了一首新歌 - 真的吗? - 是啊
- I wrote a new song. - Did you? - Yeah.
- 在洛杉矶产生的灵感 你想听听吗? - 哇 当然!
- I was inspired in LA. Want to hear it? - Wow. Yeah!
- 你有兴趣么? - 肯定的呀
- Would you be interested in that? - I would be very interested.
- 那就在那放吧 - 好激动!
- I've got it right here. - How exciting.
A Higher Place - Adam Levine
我不知道是不是我的梦想太过于简单
I don't know if I'm the fool's getting this all wrong
这只是一个完美的女孩儿和一首完美的歌
That's the dream too single,perfect girl the perfect song
我只知道的是我只能继续假装我是李斯特的朋友
All I know is I can keep on wearing Lister's guy
当你变成我的唯一也明白了我眼中的含义
When you're the only one that seeds what's read in my eyes
带我去另一个世界
Yeah take me to another space,and time
就带我去更高的地方吧
Yeah take me to a higher place
就算让我抛弃其他人我也不会介意
so I'm 'bout to get out of other ways,I don't mind
因为我知道只要遇到了你 其他一切都没了意义
You're all I know that everything's nothing to find I have you
你这是干嘛?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
你他妈是能读懂人心么?
You're like a fucking mind reader.
这是写给谁的?
Who is it for?
- Mim - 唱片公司的Mim?
- Min. - Mim from the label, Mim?
一个月前认识的那个Mim?
Mim who we met one month ago. Mim?
对
Yeah.
所以你们一起去的洛杉矶对吗?
Was she in LA with you?
嗯
Yeah.
我不知道还能说什么
I don't know what to say.
就这么发生了
It just happened.
也许会就这样自然散了
Maybe It'll go away.
也许就这样淡了
Maybe it'll fade.
但这需要一个过程
I have to see it through.
你想把枕头放这边还是那边?
Do you want to put your head on this end or this end?
你想喝点茶么?
Do you want a tea?
我不记得你是加糖还是...
I don't remember if you take sugar or....
那我想想看吧
I'm gonna wing it. I'll wing it.
拜托了 今晚跟我一起来吧
Please won't you come out with me tonight?
我今晚会唱几首歌
I'm gonna play some songs down at this open mic night.
干嘛不一起来呢?
Why don't you come with me?
因为我讨厌你的歌!
'Cause I hate your fucking songs!
我想我们都清楚这不是真的
I think we both know that isn’t true.
对不起 我不...我很喜欢你的歌
Sorry, I didn't... No, I love your songs.
我在这花太多钱了 实在有点可怕
I'm paying fucking horrendous right now...
是时候回老家了
which is exactly why I need to go home.
所以你才更需要跟我一起来
That's exactly why you need to come with me.
来吧 拜托了
Come on. I insist.
拿上那个包 我们走吧
Pick that up and come with me.
快走 我才不会让你一个人留这里
You're coming. I'm not leaving you here.
万一我回来了发现你自杀去了
If I come back, I'll find your fucking head in the oven.
女士们 先生们 今晚我带来了一位朋友
Hello, ladies and gentlemen. I have a friend here tonight.
如果你们不介意的话
And if it's okay with you
我在想要不要让她在这唱首歌?
I was wondering if you'd like her to come up here and play one of her songs.
那可以吗?
Is that okay? Yeah?
Gretta 能请你上来吗
Gretta would you come up here please?
- 你好 - 嗨
- Hello. - Hi.
- 昨晚你说要签我是 说真的吧? - 你谁?
- Were you serious last night about signing me? - Who is this?
- 啥? - 开个小玩笑 当然是真的
- Really? - I'm joking. Yeah, I was serious.
我的西装都在这儿
I have all my suits here.
亲爱的 你能不能给我找套好的西装让我打扮下
Would you get me a nice suit and make me look nice, princess.
我昨晚听到一首好歌 我告诉你
I heard a song last night and I'm telling you...
- 现在唱片公司就是需要这样的歌 - 你不能就这样冲进来 你不能这么做
- It's exactly what that shit ass record label needs right now. - You can't just barge in here.You can't come in here like this.
- 为什么? - 因为这是我们的约定 - 你屋里藏人了?
- Why? - Because that's our arrangement. - What you got somebody here?
- 不是这个问题!是我们有过协议的 - 有人吗? - 别闹了
- That's not the point! We have an arrangement. - Hello? - Stop that.
流浪的汉子啊!别担心我!
Stray man! Any stray man! Don't worry about me.
我只是个过来冲个澡的丈夫
It's just her husband taking a shower
你可以继续睡我的妻子
You can continue fucking my wife.
这并不好笑
That's not funny.
对不起 如果我真有男人的话 一定会第一个告诉你的
- Hey, I'm sorry. - If I did, you'd be the first I'd tell.
- 那你现在没有咯 - 我去帮你拿衬衫
- So you're not. - Get you a shirt and a...
不 先拿剃须刀
No, razor.
闭嘴好吗?
Stop, alright?
你想要进来吗?要一起洗吗?
You want to come in? You want sexy time?
- 准备好了吗? - 我亲爱的制作人 那我们现在去哪里?
- Ready? - So where are we going mister A and R man?
- 去找我的合伙人 让他听听你的歌 你带小样了吧? - 没有
- We're going to my partner to play him your music. You got your demo? - No.
- 你没有带样片? - 没有
- You don't have a demo? - No.
那你有My Space还是Facebook吗?
Do you have My Space or Facebook?
My Space?不不不 没有
My Space? No, I don't.
我说过的 我只是偶尔写点歌而已
I told you.I write songs from time to time.
行吧 那你写给谁啊?
Well, what do you write them for?
写给谁是什么意思?就写给我自己当兴趣呗 写给我的猫行了吧
What do you mean what for? For my pleasure. For my cat.
真的吗?他喜欢吗?
Oh, really? Does he like them?
是她 是的 她看起来很喜欢
She. Yes, she seems to.
你怎么知道?
How do you know?
因为她叫唤了
Because she purrs.
或许她是在说呸!
Maybe she's booing!
不 她很有品味的 她听见伦纳德 科恩的歌时也会叫唤
No, she purrs at Leonard Cohen too. She has very good taste.
也许她只是玩弄你
Maybe she's fucking with you.
- 我们能不谈猫了吗? - 好的 - 好
- Can we stop talking about cats now? - OK. - OK.
管他的 那就用传统的方式上吧
Fuck it. Let's do this The old-fashioned way.
你发现你在地铁里
So you find yourself at this subway
当你的世界在包装下 随身携带
When your world in a bag by your side
谢谢 Gretta 谢谢你的到来
Thank you, Gretta. Thanks for coming in.
我得跟Dan谈论一下
I'm just going to take a moment to talk with Dan for a minute.
谢谢
Thank you.
我没有很喜欢 她让我觉得不舒服
I'm not into it. It's a little undercooked for me.
她似乎有些态度的问题
She seems to have kind of an attitude problem and...
那你想要什么样的人
What are you looking for man?
所以你想要的是青少年流行歌手
You want some little teenaged pop star....
那些两岁起就让妈妈带着然后成为明星的小孩?
whose mom's been raising since two years old for stardom.
不 这不是我追求的 但你知道...
No, that's not what I'm looking for, but if you know someone...
就给我钱做个样片吧
Just give me the money to make the demo.
我会带她进棚 然后找个厉害的制作人
I'll take her into the studio. Get a hot shit producer.
再找点儿乐手 配上点儿东西...
Get a couple of session musicians, dial the thing out...
你会感受到我所感受到的她那种音乐的
and then you can hear what I'm hearing.
然后你再决定要不要让我滚蛋行么
And then you can tell me to fuck myself.
是别人给我们寄来音乐样本
People send us their demos.
而不是反过来的 我们又不负责出小样
It's not the other way around. We don't make demos.
我们是制作人 我们也是投资人
We're prospectors man. We're investors.
我们就像是在挖金矿
We're digging for gold.
先去录个小样吧 然后拿来再让我听听
Make a tape and we'll get back to you.
兄弟 我能做的也只有这些了
That's the best I can do right now, bro.
那个 我在想啊
So, I've been thinking.
为什么我们要租个一个录音棚?
Why do we even need to rent a fucking studio?
因为你需要桌子 器材 还有隔音装备?
Because you need a desk, a live room and sound proofing.
也就需要笔记本电脑 Pro Tools软件和几个麦克风
Laptop. Pro Tools. A couple of dynamic mics.
这城市就是我们的演播室
And the city is our fucking live room.
你指在室外录音?
You mean record outside?
- 没错 - 哪呢?
- That's right. - Like where?
到处都可以
Everywhere.
别管他!
Fuck him.
我们也不做小样了 直接做个专辑!
We don't need a demo. Let's record an album.
一首歌找一个地方
Every song we do in a different location.
就在纽约找就行
All over New York City.
找个夏天就能开始做
And we do it through the summer.
就献给这个
And it becomes this tribute to this...
美丽 疯狂又混乱的城市--纽约
beautiful, god damn crazy, fractured mess of a city, New York.
好啊 比如在东区的桥下
OK. Under the bridge on the lower east side.
帝国大厦的顶层
Top of the Empire State building.
中央公园湖水的船上
On rowing boats in the lake in Central Park.
唐人街 圣约翰大教堂
Chinatown. Cathedral of Saint John the Divine
还有地铁 哈姆雷区 在哪儿都行
In the subway. Fucking Harlem. Everywhere.
如果下雨怎么办
So what happens if it starts raining.
无论发生什么 都继续录下来
Whatever happens, we record it.
如果我们被逮捕了呢?
If we get arrested?
继续录啊!那太赞了!
Keep rolling! It'll be beautiful!
你喜欢么?
You like it?
你怎么想?很不错吧
What do you think? It's good.
- 你会帮我来制作么? - 我? - 恩
- Will you produce it? - Me? - Yeah.
我已经好久没做过了
I haven't produced in a long time.
我会找个年轻点的来做
We'll get somebody young to produce it.
- 不 我想要你来做 - 为什么?
- No, but I want you to do it. - Why?
我就是想让你来
Because I do.
我有弦乐器 但我们很需要个钢琴 然后还有吉他
I give you strings, but we definitely need piano. Then with the guitars underneath.
- 好的 我喜欢 - 好的 - 好的
- Got it. I love it. - Done. - Done.
世界第一辆捷豹手机音乐工作室诞生了
The world's first Jag mobile recording studio. It's done.
太有才了!
It's bloody genius it is!
你要去哪儿?
Where do you want to go?
我们需要些音乐人
We need musicians.
无聊又悲惨的音乐人
Terminally, miserably bored musicians.
之后我觉得...
After that I think...
你先弹奏小提琴和大提琴 先大提琴再小提琴
then you bring in the violin and cello. First cello then violin.
直到主音吉他响起来的时候 我想把它混成不同的声音效果
When we get into that lead guitar thing, I want it to become
a whole different kind of sound.
这个是Malcolm 他是个神童
This is Malcolm. Malcolm is a child prodigy.
他从五岁就开始拉小提琴了
He's been playing violin since he was five years old.
- 确切的说是我从四岁就开始了 - 四岁
- I technically started when I was four. - Four.
这是他的姐姐Rachel
And this is his older sister, Rachel.
她就读于曼哈顿音乐学院 还拿全额奖学金
She's at the Manhattan School of Music on a full scholarship.
- 他们班最出色的大提琴手 - 这太棒了
- Top of her class cellist. - That's amazing.
事情是这样的
So here's the deal.
我没法先付给你们工资
I can't afford to pay you up front.
所以 我想和你们先签合同 之后再付钱给你们
So I want to offer you a legitimate back end deal.
可以吗?
Sound good?
好吧 只要它不是什么狗屁古典音乐就行
Yeah, as long as it's not fucking Vivaldi.
当然不会是那破玩意儿
It's not fucking Vivaldi.
不错 不 不 这太赞了
It's great. No, no, no. It's great.
当然 必须有钢琴声 在吉他的部分切入
Definitely need piano. Like fill in the guitar underneath.
是啊 你说的对
You got it. I love it.
Steve 太美丽了
Steve, beautiful.
- Zach 这是干什么? - 我不干了 - 姑娘们 祝你们好运 - 保持联系
- Zach. What's going on? - I quit. - Good lucks, girls. - Keep in touch.
吉他的下一段
When we get into that lead guitar thing.
我想把它混成不同的声音效果
I want it to become a whole different kind of sound.
我想要那种朋克加上流行音乐的那种感觉
I want it to be punk meets pop.
嗨起来!
And have some fun!
他到了
Ah, he's home.
Dan 还好么 兄弟?
Dan, what's up, man?
Troublegum 我的兄弟 有了你什么都解决了
Troublegum, my brother. My troubles are over.
还给我客气什么啊
What say you give me some love, man.
就是这里了!这里简直是帮派的天堂啊 看到你真高兴
This is it! Gangsta paradise. I'm glad to see you.
谢谢 虽然我不认识你 但还是让我来抱一下
Thanks to you. Give me a hug. I don' t know you.
这是Gretta
That's Gretta.
很棒的歌手 作曲人
Great singer and songwriter.
- 再抱一下 - 再一个?
- Let's get another one. - Another one? Oh!
你都哪儿了?这都两三年没见了
Where have you been? It's been two or years.
我一点也不喜欢这样
I don't appreciate this shit.
停滞不前的 做点这个 做点那个呗
Been on the down low a little bit. Doing this. Doing that.
等待一个新的机会
Waiting for the next move.
期待着再一次的最佳状态
Anticipating the next groove.
我知道你想证明些什么 是吧?
I know you got a lot of shit to prove, right?
私下里 找寻着那一个好声音
Been on the underground, looking for that new sound.
我们可不能再徘徊下去了
We ain't fucking around.
不管是对是错
'Cause if it ain't right then it's wrong.
路还长
And the road is long
下一步走出前
and you're only as strong
你会知道你自己有多强大
as your next move.
- 感觉对么? - 挺对的
- You feel that? - That's pretty much it.
这就像什么超自然现象一样
Damn. That was like some paranormal activity.
反正你懂我的
You know me.
- 我真是太高兴见到你了 老兄 Jimmy 你把刚刚那词儿记下来了没? - 放心 记下了
- I'm just so happy to see you, man. Yo! Fat Jimmy, did you get that down? - Yeah, I got it.
刚刚那一段儿真够棒的 宝贝儿 来 拉着我手
'Cause that was exceptionally good. Hold my hand, baby. Come on.
老兄 我该怎么帮你?
How can I help you, brother?
一个户外的专辑!这主意太赞了!
An outdoor album! That's fucking crazy.
我怎么就想不到这么棒的主意呢 你想要我做什么?
I wish I could have thought of that. What do you want me to do?
我需要的音乐人 我还需要贝司手和鼓手
I need musicians. I need a base player and a drummer.
我这儿音乐人多着呢
I got plenty of musicians.
问题是我们没钱请他们
The problem is we can't pay them.
- 管他呢 我来付钱就行了 - 为什么?
- Fuck it. I'll pay them. - Why?
什么为什么?我这是为了他
What do you mean why? For him.
当然
Of course.
- 来吧 跳进泳池吧 - 别碰我 小心我杀了你
- Come on. Get your sexy self in the pool. - No. Don't touch me. I will kill you.
她是英国人 有些保守
She's English. She's a little uptight.
- Gretta 我祝你专辑一切顺利 - 谢谢
- Good luck on the album, Gretta. - Thank you.
你看这儿的别墅 跑车什么的
Everything you see around here. This crib. These cars.
都是因为他
They're because of him.
- 我永远不会忘记的 - 我明白了 - 不 不 不
- I don't ever forget that. - I get it. - No, no, no.
你可不会了解的
You can't know.
像他那样的人 出名几年后
A guy like that falls on his luck for a couple of years.
人们压根就不会记得他是谁
People lose sight of who he is.
人们不尊重他 但他确实值得我们尊重
And they don't treat him with the respect. He deserves.
他说的都是废话
Anything he's saying is bullshit.
有事就来联系我
Anything you need, okay?
我太爱你了 感谢你
I love you, man. Thank you.
我喜欢她
I like her.
你确定么?这儿的杂音你听见了么?
Are you serious? Are you listening to this?
我们要把杂音用进去 会很棒的
We're gonna use it. It's gonna be genius.
你就是个天才 我不用担心的
You're a genius. I don't have any fear.
你听不见我都听到了些什么
You don't hear what I hear.
你会让我脑中的音乐变成现实的
You're gonna make it real. I love it.
开始吧?
Got it?
- 音轨里全是那群孩子的声音 - 你说什么?
- Those kids are gonna be all over this track. - What do you mean?
帮我拿下这个
Take this.
小屁孩们 来来来
Little children. Yo! Yo! Yo!
打扰一下啊
Let me see this for a second.
我正在录制一首歌
I'm shooting a song down here
- 能帮我个忙 安静五分钟吗? - 没门
- and I need you guys to be quiet for five minutes? - No way, man.
我给钱
I'll pay you.
- 多少? - 每人一美元
- How much? - A buck each.
你真搞笑 五块钱
Hey, you're funny. Five dollars.
是给你们所有人五块钱嘛?好吧 两块钱! 每个孩子两块钱
Five bucks for all of you guys? Okay. Two bucks! Two bucks each.
不!
No!
好 每人五美元
All right. Five bucks each.
那你给我们每个人五块钱和五个棒棒糖
Bring us five bucks and five lollipops. One for each of us.
或者一包香烟和打火机也行
Throw in a box of cigarettes and lighter.
我给你们所有人一包烟 你们分着抽
I'll give you one cigarette for each of you to smoke and you share it.
还有一盒火柴 行么?
And I ll give you a pack of matches. All right?
- 好的 - 你们会唱歌么?
- Yes. - Can you sing?
Coming Up Roses - Keira Knightley
当你临睡前
When you were asleep
我出去散步
And I was out walking
一串声音在你耳边响起
The voices started to speak
他们会一直讲下去
And they wouldn't stop talking
这是一种征兆
There were signs all around
打乱了我的思绪
It really got my mind racing
没错 你一直都挺孤单的
You were right all along
是时候做出些改变了
Something's gotta change
坚持
Hold on
继续坚持 这并不适合你
Hold on. They're not for me
继续坚持下去
Hold on
因为一切都会顺利起来
Cause everything's coming up roses
顺利
Roses
我们又回到了街道上
We were back on the street
因为听到了首不错的歌
Found a song that's worth singing
当你胜利之钟敲响前
The blur that knows a defeat
你总会听到些失败的杂音在耳中盘旋
While your victory bell's ringing
我一直不懈的
My whole life's turned around
追寻人生的意义 你一直都挺孤单的
For this thing you keep chasing. You were right all along
是时候做出些改变了
It's me who's got to change
坚持
Hold on
继续坚持 这并不适合你
Hold on. They're not for me
继续坚持下去
Hold on
因为一切进展都会顺利起来
'Cause everything's coming up roses
(Hold on, hold on)
就是这样!就是这样!
Yes! Yes! That was it.
简直太棒了!
Yes! It's gonna work!
天啊!那就是帝国大厦嘛?
Oh my God! Is that the Empire State?
是啊 就是这儿
Yeah, right here.
- 我们摆在这里 然后站在那里 - 非常好 - 是啊
Set up here. Get that. - It's really good. - Yeah.
- 太棒了 - 风会不会有问题?
- Great. - The wind's good, right?
不算特别响 没事的
It's not too loud. It's good.
还可以看见别人家的窗口 真是太有趣了
And we can look into people's windows, which is always fun.
- 你想跟我一起去接Violet吗? - 可以吗? - 可以啊 走吧
- You want to come with me to get Violet? - Is that Okay? - Yeah. Come on.
好兄弟 来给你
My brother. There you go.
太感谢了
Thank you very much.
她来了
That's her.
- 这是Gretta 就是我和你说的那个音乐人 - 你好吗?
- This is Gretta. She's the song writer I was telling you about. - How are you doing?
那个穿蓝色T恤的帅哥是谁?
So who was the cute guy? The one in the blue shirt.
Greg 你注意到他了?
Greg. You noticed him?
当然啊 他那么帅怎么可能注意不到
Sure. Who wouldn't? He's gorgeous.
他真的遥不可及
He's totally out of our league.
你无法接近他?
He's out of your league?
但看着并不像这样啊
He didn't look out of your league.
忽视他吧
Ignore him.
你怎么让别人注意到你在忽视他们
How can you get someone to notice you're ignoring them
如果他们在忽视你呢?
if they're ignoring you?
他没有忽视你啦 你那么漂亮
He's not ignoring you. You're beautiful.
他知道你在这儿 他只是在等待靠近你的机会
He knows you're there. He's just hedging his bets.
但你必须确定你是真的很喜欢他
You have to be sure that you actually like him.
确定他不是那种只适合在学校里交往的人
He's not just the guy in school to be seen with.
我确实挺喜欢他的
No, I do really like him.
那你快想个办法让他约你出去啊
Well, then, you have to find a way to get him to ask you out.
那我该怎么做?
Yes, but how?
首先不要穿得像个很随便的女生啊
Well, for starters, stop dressing like you're totally easy!
我还以为这样看起来会性感点 这可是American Apparel的衣服啊
I thought this was sort of sexy. It's American Apparel.
的确是性感的 非常 非常性感
It is sort of sexy. It's very, very sexy.
- 但这看起来一点神秘感都没有 你懂么? - 也许吧
- But it doesn't leave much to the imagination. You know? - I guess.
- 你想去逛街吗? - 好啊 - 是吗? - 恩
- You want to go shopping? - I do. - Yeah? - Yeah.
- 好的 - 我们要去逛街
- Okay, good. - We're going shopping.
- 谢谢 - 谢谢
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- 祝你的专辑好运 听起来很不错 - 谢谢
- Good luck with the rest of your album. It sounds cool. - Thank you.
- 你有钥匙吗? - 有
- You have your key? - Yep.
你也可以来加入我们录音啊
Hey you should come sing on a track?
可我不会唱歌
I can't sing.
不过我会弹点吉他
I can play like a bit of guitar.
真的吗?我们周四会开始录歌
Can you? We're doing one on Thursday.
- 挺简单的 你可以来试下啊 - 爸爸可以吗?
- It will be really simple. You should come and play. - Can I dad?
我再考虑一下
I need to contemplate that.
你这是在干什么?干嘛这样做?
What are you doing? That ain't cool.
我都不知道她吉他有没好到能录在专辑里
I don't know if she can play guitar well enough to play on a track.
- 如果到时候弹不好会让她很尴尬的 - 放心吧 挺简单的 让她来吧
- I don’t won’t to embarrass her. What if she can't play? - Look, it's going to be easy. Let her do it.
- 谁啊? - 是我
- Yeah? - Hey, babe.
Violet呢?
Where's Violet?
Violet?
我在想啊 你认为我周四录歌让她来弹吉他怎样?
I was wondering...You think it would be cool if she came and played guitar on a song I'm recording on Thursday?
她弹的蛮难听的
She's terrible on guitar.
- 应该不差吧 - 她真的很糟糕 - 我觉得应该没问题
- She's not bad. - She's terrible. - I think she'll be okay.
- 什么时候? - 五点 你能带她来吗?
- When will she...? - Five o'clock. Will you bring her?
- 你决定吧 - 好
- It's up to you. - Yeah.
我把地址发给你 要不你也来吧
I'll text you the address. Why don't you come to?
不可能
No way.
来吧 会很有趣的
Come on. Just come. It'll be fun.
- 而且我希望你能来 - 我考虑下吧
- I want you to come. - I'll think about it.
- 我可能会去的 - 谢谢
- I'll come, maybe. - Thank you.
今天很开心能见到你和Violet在一起
It's nice to see you with Violet today.
不能经常看见她 你一定很痛苦吧
It must be hard not seeing her more.
是啊
Yeah.It's...
那你为什么不经常去看看她?
So why don't you?
很显然她需要爸爸在她身边
She obviously really needs her father around.
你在当社工教育我么?
What are you the fucking Social Services now?
没啦 我只是想说...
No. I mean I'm just saying...
对你来说离开一定很痛苦吧
It must have been fairly tense for you to leave.
尤其是当看到她现在有多么需要你的时候
Especially seeing as how much she obviously wants you around.
我要走了 明早见吧
I'm gonna split. I'll see you tomorrow morning.
搞什么啊
Fuck, man.
Dan?抱歉 我错了
Dan? Hey, look. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
那你想要我怎样?你在玩什么小把戏?
What do you want from me? What game are you playing?
你什么意思?我只是...
What does that mean? I just...
- 什么? - 只是我今天看见她那么可爱
- What? - I saw how sweet she was today
觉得你不能和她在一起实在是太可惜了
and I just felt sorry for you being away from that.
你有病吧 你就自己做出这样的判断
That is such a crock of shit. You were back there judging me.
你说的好像是我离开他们...
You think that I left that relationship...
就因为我是个自私的混蛋吗?
because I'm some sort of selfish, depressed prick?
虽然我就是这样
Which I am, by the way.
没啊 我不认为你是一个自私的混蛋
No. I don't think you're a selfish, depressed prick.
我只是觉得你让自己的问题影响到你的生活罢了
I think you've let your troubles get in the way of your entire life.
你太幼稚了
Oh, babe. You're really showing your age right now.
你完全不清楚两个经历18年婚姻生活的夫妻
You have no idea what happens between two people
究竟发生了什么事情
after 18 years of marriage.
这是因为你愿意和一个出轨了的傻逼交往
And because you're willing to hang around for some asshole
就认为全天下的男人都是这样的吗?那是你自己的事了
after he totally betrayed you, that's your business.
不 我很抱歉 你说的没错
Oh no. I'm sorry. You're right.
我为那段感情付出了很多!
I put a lot of time and effort into that relationship.
不!我不会因为一点小障碍就离开的
And no! I'm not walking away just because of a bump in the road!
小障碍?
Bump in the road?
我离开是因为她伤透了我的心
I left that relationship 'cause I was having a nervous breakdown.
她出去跟别的男人上床
And she was out there fucking some other guy
而且她打算和那个男的在一起
planning how she was gonna start a whole new life with him.
而当时我却在照顾我的孩子!
when I was here taking care of my kid!
所以你一点儿也不清楚你在说什么!
You have no fucking clue what you're talking about!
你什么都不知道!
You know nothing!
她就出差了一年
She goes a year up to work on a junket.
就爱上了一个歌手
And she ends up meeting and falling in love with this singer.
他们爱得不能自拔 产生了爱情的冲动和火花
Bang. Boom. Thunder, lightning, fireworks. The whole bit.
他们计划各自回家
And the arrangement was that they were gonna come back
告诉各自的配偶关于他们相爱的事情
and tell their partners that they had fallen in love
他们还准备共度一生
and they're gonna spend the rest of their lives together.
等我赶到机场迎接她时
And so I go to the airport to pick her up
她就把一切都向我坦白了
and she just comes out with it first off. Whole story.
第二天 她的行李就都打包好了
Then next day her bags are all packed
- 我们就告诉了Violet发生了什么 - 然后呢 发生了什么事?
- and we're telling Violet what's going to happen. - So what did happen?
他忍着对这份爱情的渴望 登上了飞机又重新回到自己的生活中
He choked. He got on the airplane. Went back to his life.
他关掉了手机 然后就这样消失了
Turned his phone off and she never heard from him again.
我搬到了另一个房间去住
I move into another bedroom.
而她则在等待一个永远不会打来的电话
She's waiting around for a phone call that never comes.
我很生气...
And I turn into a...
然后就变成了现在这个样子
I lose my shit a little bit.
- 对不起 - 没事
- So sorry. - No.
也许干音乐这行的
Maybe people in the music industry don't
就不能成为一个好的伴侣或者是一个好父亲
just don't make good life partners or fathers.
嗯 看起来是的
Yeah. It certainly looks that way.
- 不能成为一个好爸爸倒说不定 我觉得你是一个非常好的父亲 - 是啊
- I didn't mean about the father's bit. You make a very good father. - Yeah, right.
可能只是不是好搭档
Maybe just not a good partner.
这个是什么
What is that?
这个?这是个分频器
This? That's a splitter.
一个源能插两个耳机
For two headphones go into one input.
- 这是我第一次和Miriam约会时用的 - It is?
- It's actually from my first date with Miriam. - 是吗?
你们在哪相遇的?
Where'd you meet?
我们听着她的CD 在城市里一起慢慢散步
We walked all over the city, listening to her CD player.
我感觉我们整个晚上都没怎么说过话
I don't think we said more than two words to each other the whole night.
那时是除夕 两个月后 我们就结婚了
That was New Year's Eve and we were married two months later.
挺好的
That's lovely.
你手机里有什么歌?
What kind of music you got on your phone?
我不会跟你分享我的音乐的 绝对不会
I'm not giving you access to my music library. I'm really not.
- 里面有很多尴尬的歌 - 我也是
- There's a lot of embarrassing, very guilty pleasures in there. - Mine too.
你可以通过他听的歌了解这个人的很多方面
You can tell a lot about a person by what's on their playlist.
我就是知道这一点 才让我觉得担心的
I know you can. That's what's worrying me.
所以能听听看吗?
So are we gonna do this?
好 来吧!
Okay. Let's do it
听起来不错!
This is a really good choice!
- 很完美 对不对? - 是啊
- Oh yeah. Genius. Perfect. Right? - Yeah. Yeah.
不!不对!
Oh no! I forgot the words!
- 这时候该跳舞了 - 什么?
- Okay! Okay, we've got to dance. - What?
我们必须要跳舞!
We've got to dance!
- 好吧 我们要跳舞了 - 我们要跳舞了!
- Okay, we've got to dance. - We've gotta dance!
来这边
This way.
我怕你会觉得这首歌有点俗气
I'm quite frightened 'cause you might find this cheesy
但是这是我最喜欢的电影里的一首歌
but it is one of my favorite songs from one of my favorite films.
你准备好了吗?
Are you ready?
很棒对吧?
It's good, right?
- 这就是我为什么喜欢音乐 - 什么?
- That's what I love about music. - What?
生活中最普通的一幕 突然间
One of the most banal scenes is suddenly invested
就充满了这么多的意义
with so much meaning.
所有的那些琐事
All these banalities.
因为音乐
They're suddenly turned into these...
他们突然变成了
these beautiful
闪亮无暇的珍珠
effervescent pearls.
我必须说 当我越来越老时 这些珍珠
I've gotta say, as I've gotten older these pearls
对我来说越来越稀有珍贵
are just becoming increasingly more and more rare to me.
线比珍珠链多?
More string than pearls?
那你要收集到够多的珍珠才行
You've got to travel over a lot more string to get to the pearls.
这一刻便是珍珠啊 Gretta
This moment is a pearl, Gretta.
也算吧?
It sort of is, isn't it?
对 这些都是珍珠
All of this has been a pearl.
- 大家好! - Hi
- Hey guys! - 嗨
你好啊 Steve
Hello Steve.
- 快来看看这个 你男友刚获得了个音乐奖 - 不可能吧
- Come on and check it out. Your boyfriend just won a Music Gong. - No way.
简直不敢相信
You won't believe it.
他的脸怎么了
He's done something to his face.
哇 非常感谢大家
Wow. Thank you so much.
我有点困惑和惊讶我能获得这个奖 这太棒了
I'm a bit taken aback by this. This is incredible.
但这证明了一个人
It just proves that a guy from nowhere
可以真的成功如果他一直追求在梦想
can actually make it if he follows his dreams.
老实讲 这段话
I've been practicing this speech
我已经在浴室里拿着我的香波练习了无数遍了
into a shampoo bottle in the shower my entire life.
- 天 谢谢你们 - 胡子不错 你个傻逼
- Gosh. Thank you. - Nice beard, you fucking loser.
什么梦想?
What dreams?
我们从来没有做过那样的梦想 我不记得有那样的梦想
We never had those dreams. I don't remember those dreams.
- 你怎么知道? - 因为我了解他
- How do you know? - Because, I know him.
也许是他个人的梦想
Maybe they were private dreams.
只不过他从来没告诉过你
Maybe he just never told you about them.
可是我跟那个人一起生活了五年呀?
Who was I living with for the last five years?
你一直在跟一个摇滚明星生活 只是他并不自知罢了
Baby, you've been living with a rock star. Only he didn't know it.
无所谓 但现在他找到了自我 我告诉你
It didn't matter. But now that he does, I've gotta tell you
这些人都很爱这种感觉
these people get married to it.
他们爱上了音乐 爱上了聚光灯 走上了这条路
They fall in love with the music. They fall in love with the lights. They fall in love with the road.
爱上了一切乱七八糟的东西 无论他如何努力
All that shit. And no matter how hard he tries
他都不会让女人快乐起来的
he's never gonna be able to make a woman happy.
- 好了 明早见 - 再见
- See you in the morning. - See you.
他为什么这样做呢?
Why would he do that?
我不知道 谁会这样做呢?
I don't know. Why would anyone?
我来告诉你他为什么这样做吧
I'll tell you why he did it.
因为他想成为那种会说
'Cause he wants to look like the guy who doesn't realize it.
"我的胡子这么长了!
"Oh! I've grown a beard!
我太忙了 沉浸在歌曲创作中
I was so busy, lost inside myself writing music
没有意识到我的胡须已经长到脖子这里了"
I didn't realize I'd grown a beard the size of my neck."
这样想来我那时真是太傻了
I'm gonna sound quite cheesy over it.
像个傻瓜一样爱着他
I loved him like a fool.
我可不认为你是个傻瓜 我感觉那听起来像首很不错的歌
I don't think that's cheesy. I think that sounds like a phenomenal song.
- 是吗? - 是的 就像一首歌
- Does it? - It sounds like a song.
我觉得你应该写出来 现在就写出来
I think it sounds like a song that you should write right now.
You should write it down.
写下来
Write it down.
- 写下来 用你的灵感 快说你现在真有灵感 - 好的 我现在灵感喷发
- Write it down, 'cause you're in the zone. Say it, I'm in the zone. - I'm in the zone.
不要写那种你是什么漂亮的英国女孩
Don't say it like you're those posh English girls.
来纽约写歌 就写我现在灵感爆发
Say it like someone in New York. Say, I'm in the fucking zone.
- 你写下来"我就是感觉来了才写歌" - 我就是感觉来了才写歌
- Say "I'm in the fucking zone." - I'm in the fucking zone.
我要写首歌 不管是什么
I've gotta write a song. And I don't give a shit.
- 我就是要写一首歌 - 好啦 快闭嘴
- I'm gonna write a song. - No, actually shut up.
好了 我不说话了 我不说话
All right. I'm shushing. I'm shushing.
已拨 好了 准备开始
Dialing. All right, here we go.
打开免提
Speaker.
我是Dave Kohl
Hey, this is Dave Kohl.
我在忙着干大事接不了电话
I am probably busy doing something awesome
有事请留言
so leave me a message
但我也许永远也不会看
and I probably won't be able to get back to you at all. Ever.
Like a Fool - Keira Knightley
我们会时不时的在爱情中冒冒险
We take a chance from time to time
有时简直就是自找麻烦
And put our necks out on the line
你已经打破了一个个
And you have broken every promise
彼此间的承诺
that we made
愚蠢的是我居然一直爱着你
And I have loved you anyway
选择了这么一个好时机离开我
Took a fine time to leave me hangin' out to dry
把我晾在一边
Understand now I'm greivin'
走吧 别再浪费我的时间
So don't you waste my time
你已经拿走了我的一切
Cause you have taken
我的人生旅途就这么停止了
All the wind out from my sails
愚蠢的是我却一直爱着你
And I have loved you just the same
我们的爱刚刚萌发 你却这么走了
We finally find this then you're gone
我只能继续追寻人生的美好
Been chasin' rainbows all along
而你却怪罪于我
And you have cursed me
当我们都不应该被谴责的时候
When there's no one left to blame
愚蠢的是我还是那么爱你
And I have loved you just the same
你已经打破了
And you have broken
一个个该死的规定
every single fucking rule
愚蠢的是我居然还是那么爱你
And I have loved you like a fool
再来首?
One more?
介绍一下这是Miriam
Hey. Everybody! This is Miriam.
这是Gretta
This is Gretta.
这是我的女儿Violet
This is my daughter Violet.
Miriam 谢谢
Miriam. Thank you.
这不算高吧
It's not too high is it?
这对贝斯来说不算高的吧
It's not too high for a bass. Exactly.
如果要这样的话 根本不会有人想要玩贝斯
No one should play bass unless it's this high.
要我调放大声音 还是这样就好?
You want me to set your amp or are you good?
不不不 等等 等等
Hold up. Hold up. Hold up.
Rachel 最开始的时候 加快一点没关系
Rachel. At the top, come in a little more gradually.
- Jimmy! - 什么事? - 给点力 - 好吧 我知道了
- Bad Jimmy! - Yo, what's up? - Come on, man. - All right. I got you.
- 警察不会追到这儿来的 让我听听低音 - 好好好 放心吧
- The police ain't gonna get you up here. Let's hear that bass. - I got you, baby. I got you.
抱歉 等一等 你是不是能弹贝司?
I'm sorry. Wait a minute. Do you play bass?
你跑题了 不行
You were out of tune. You are flat.
我在网上看见的 你以前好像是弹贝司的
Because I read on the internet that you used to play bass.
所以既然已经让Violet弹吉他了
If we can get Violet doing some guitar on this.
这应该是家庭事务了吧
This should be a family affair.
我不弹贝斯所以我才是个制作人
I'm a producer 'cause I don't play bass, baby.
来吧 你得做的 你要弹的
Yes you are! You gotta do it. You gotta do it!
好吧!好吧!
All right! All right!
你想要弹的时候就插进来吧
Come in whenever you want. You can wait.
很简单的
Just keep it simple.
我不知道要弹什么
I don't know if I'm gonna play.
随便 你想怎么弹就怎么弹 好吗?
Whatever. If you feel like it you do it. Okay?
完全没问题的 不要有压力想着去怎么做
It's totally cool. But don't feel like you have to overdo it
或者想去证明什么 这些家伙们都是的...
or prove anything to anybody. These guys are all...
Dave Kohl
语音邮件和未接来电
大伙们 抱歉 我们能休息五分钟吗?
Guys. Sorry. Can we take five?
- 好的 休息五分钟吧 - 是五分钟 不是十分钟
- All right. Let's take five. - Five, not ten.
我回纽约开演唱会了
Hey. I'm back in New York for a gig.
我听到你唱歌的电话留言了 我必须见你
I got your singing message. I have to see you.
回我电话 请一定回我电话
Call me. Please call me.
Tell Me If You Wanna Go Home - Keira Knightley
也许你不必如此的友善
Oh maybe you don't have to kill so kind
假装来治愈我的心 但其实你并不会这样
pretend to ease my mind when baby you won't
亲爱的 你不必甜言蜜语
Oh sugar, you don't have to be so sweet
我知道你会遇见谁
I know who you're going to meet
别说我不会知道
Don't say that I don't
也许我不会让对你的回忆困扰我
So maybe I won't let your memory haunt me
我会和孤独一起去梦游
I'll be sleep walking with the lonely
如果你带我回家
If you taking me home
告诉我是否这是我自己的家
tell me if I'm back to my own
并且还给我曾经借给你的心
Giving back a heart that's on loan
如果你想回家就告诉我
Just tell me if you wanna go home
告诉我你想回家
Tell me if you wanna go home
因为我不太确定 (告诉我是否这是我自己的家)
'cause I'm just not sure (tell me if I'm back to my own)
如果回到曾经
how to get back there
还给我曾借给你的心
Giving back a heart that's on loan
如果你要带我回家
If you taking me home
请告诉我这就是我的家
tell me if I'm back to my own
还给我曾借给你的心
Giving back a heart that's on loan
告诉我你是否打算回家
just tell me if you wanna go wanna go wanna go wanna go wanna
因为我不太确定 我们是否回得到从前
'cause I'm just not sure how to get back there
而且我再也无法承受 如果你不在那里
and I just can't bear if you're not there
因为我不太确定
'cause I'm just not sure
告诉我是否回到我自己的家 (该怎么回去)
Tell me if I'm back to my own (How to get back there)
还给我曾借给你的心 (只是我再也无法承受)
Giving back a heart that's on loan (and I just can't bear)
如果你想回家就告诉我 (如果你不在那里)
Just tell me if you wanna go home (if you're not there)
(因为我不太确定)
(Cause I'm just not sure)
(该怎么回去)
(How to get back there)
(只是我再也无法承受)
(And I just can't bear)
(如果你不在那里)
(If you're not there)
把该死的音乐关小点!
Turn down that fucking music!
再给我们三分钟!
Give us three more minutes!
我报警了
I'm calling the cops.
别报警
Don't call the cops.
我的天!Violet 太棒了!
Oh my God! Oh, Violet!
警察来了!来吧 我们撤!
And now the police! Come on, let's go.
- 你好 - 恭喜
- Hello. - Congratulations.
谢谢 我们该干一杯 来吧
Thank you. We should have a toast. Right now.
敬你的专辑?
To your album?
是我们的专辑
To our album.
是么?
Really?
不要高兴得太早 我只是尝试着戒
Don't get too excited. I'm just trying it out.
所以要用这个干么?
Should we toast to that?
为什么有人会喝这玩意儿?
God damn. How do people drink that?
我们来玩个游戏
We're going to play a game.
我来放一首一定会让人想跳舞的歌
I'm going to play a song that is impossible to not dance to.
看看有谁能听着这歌忍住不跳舞
I defy you not to dance to this song.
听起来不错啊
This is good.
我知道你想跳!我知道你想跳!
You know you want to! You know you want to!
我知道你想!你很想跳吧!
Oh, you know you want to! You do!
来吧!来吧!
Oh! There it is! There it is!
我要送他们回家
I'm gonna give them a ride home.
- 晚安 - 晚安
- Good night. - Good night.
谢谢你做的一切
Thank you for everything.
不谢谢你做的一切。
No, thank you for everything.
好吧 混蛋 找个地方见面吧
OK asshole, let's meet.
巡演怎么样?
So how was touring?
巡演很赞 很累 也很煎熬
Touring was amazing. Grueling. Punishing.
但又鼓舞人心
Inspiring.
- 在巡演里找到自己了么? - 我不知道
- Did you find yourself? - I don't know.
看来你找到了个大胡子
Well, you certainly found a beard anyway.
看看
Look at that thing.
- 是有点夸张 - 真的好多
- It's intense. - It's big.
Mim跟你一起巡演了吗?
Did Mim go with you? On tour?
- 所以 你想直接就谈这个么? - 是啊 - 好吧
- You just wanna go straight into this then? - Yeah. - Yeah.
你们现在过得很幸福吗?还是你...
Are you the happiest couple ever? Or did you...
一个月后分手了 她上车回到了纽约
break up after a month and she came back to New York on a bus.
其实是火车
It was a train actually.
对不起 我有点太贱了
I'm sorry. I'm being a bitch.
不会
No.
确实是这样
You're entitled.
那你呢 你最近在做什么?
So, what've you been up to?
坚持
Hold on
坚持下去 这并不是我想要的
Hold on. Hold they're not for me
天 这简直太棒了 Gretta
God. It's amazing, Gretta.
- 真的吗? - 真的 背景音 还有这个城市
- Really? - Totally. Ambient sound. The city.
- 就是只有这样了是吧?没有后期修声?什么都没有? - 不 不 不会了 就你听到的这样
- And that's it? No over-dubs? Nothing? - No, no, no. It's just the way you hear it.
真的很棒
God, it's so great.
他们有跟你签合同么?
And they're really offering you a deal?
没有...我不知道 他必须先给他的合伙人听听看 然后再看情况吧
No...Well, I don't know. He has to play it to his partner first. So, we'll see.
我真不敢相信他对你的歌做了些什么
I can not believe what he's done with your songs.
我也觉得他太棒了
I know. He's amazing.
你应该让他帮你做专辑
You should get him to do your record.
不行了 太晚了
Ah, it's too late.
已经刚刚在洛杉矶完成了在做后期制作了
I just finished mastering the record in LA.
我们沿途录制过来的
Yeah, I recorded in various studios on the road.
哇 那么 专辑名是什么?
Wow. So what's it called?
"在路上"
"On the Road"
所以 这就像杰克 凯鲁亚克的书一样
So it's kind of like Kerouac.
是啊
Yeah.
- 是的 没错 实在是无聊得可怕的专辑名 - 不会
- Yeah it is. That's actually a terrible album name. - No.
我是说 对他来说就还行
I mean. It worked for him.
总之就是差劲
No. It's bad.
我知道你觉得这很无聊
I know that you now it's bad.
没有 我...
No. I'm...
你想听听吗?
Would you like to go hear it?
- 我很乐意听 - 好的
- I would love to hear it. - OK.
若夜空中星辰不再相互凝望闪烁
But are we all lost stars
将如何继续照亮黑暗
trying to light up the dark?
我想我是看见你哭了
And I thought I saw you out there crying
我想我听到了你呼唤着我的名字
and I thought I heard you call my name
我想我是看见你哭了
and I thought i heard you out there crying
还是一成不变
just the same
好了 你有什么感想?
All right. What do you think?
我想我需要再听一次
I think I need to listen to it again.
不 不 我想要你对这首歌的第一印象
No, no. I want your immediate reaction.
第一印象?
My immediate reaction?
好吧
Okay.
我觉得这首歌好像失魂了 你知道吗?
I think that you've lost the songs in the production, you know?
就好像这歌名"Lost Stars"
I mean. Okay, takes "Lost Stars".
我写的是一首民谣
I wrote it as a ballad.
现在 这听起来像一首流行歌曲
And it sounds like a piece of stadium pop.
是啊 但是 我想让这首歌成为热门单曲
Yeah but, I wanted to turn it into a hit.
- 为什么? - 什么为什么呢?这是什么问题呢?
- Why? - Why? What kind of question is that?
你是作者 你的名字将被记录在歌曲作家中 Gretta
You're the writer. You get sole writing credit on it, Gretta.
这对你来说是一个很好的机会
This is huge for you.
是的 但这样这首歌就失去了它的本意 这首歌很微妙的
Yeah,bI mean, but you weren't supposed to lose the song in it. It's delicate.
- 我真的觉得你应该重录 - 是啊 但是 大家都喜欢这样的 他们觉得很棒
- I really think you should get it remixed. - Yeah, but everyone loves it when we do it. It's amazing.
你必须看看他们现场的反应 房间里的气氛都变了
You have to come see it live. The reaction to it. The energy in the room just changes.
为什么你这么在意别人的想法?
Why are you so worried about what other people think?
这是我们的歌
It's our song.
是的 但是音乐的存在不就是为了与他人分享么
It is, but isn't that what music is about? Sharing it with people.
不 不能是这首歌 Dave
No, not that song, Dave.
好吧 所以那这是要代入谁?
Okay. Well, good. Then who do we get to remix this?
Mim 也许你应该把Mim代入进去
Mim. Maybe you should get Mim to remix it.
- 真的吗?这明显跟专辑很没有关系 - 你这么觉得?
- Really? So this is obviously not anything about the album. - You think?
你看 这就是做音乐的情侣总会发生的
Don't become this music biz couple, you know?
争辩 关于我们的专辑
Arguing about our albums.
但可笑的是
The funny thing about all this
我可以把这张该死的专辑扔到海里去
is that I would throw that fucking record into the ocean
如果我们还可以继续现在的对话
if we could just continue this conversation right now.
这也是我想表达的 好么?
This is what I want to talk about. Okay?
而且如果我能以任何形式
And if I could somehow say something or do anything
来弥补我做过的对不起我们的事
that would undo what I did to us
请告诉我怎样做 拜托了
Just tell me what it is. Help me.
你会做吗?
Would you?
你会把它扔进大海吗?
Would you throw it in the ocean?
你希望我这么做么?
Would you want me to?
算了
No.
我觉得...我觉得一切都变了
No, I think...I think everything's changed.
- 我只是觉得很难再调整回来 - 我知道
- And I'm just finding it a big hard to adjust. - I know.
这说得通 但我们会找到一个方法来
It makes sense. But we're just gonna have to find a way to
解决这个问题 一起
get through this. Get through this together.
你什么时候开始有这样的觉悟的?
When did you realize that?
当我听到你唱的到语音邮件
When you sang to me on my voicemail.
我意识到 在这个地球上没有人
And I realized that nobody on Earth in their right mind
能像你一样远程控制我的感情
would ever do anything remotely like that.
太让我难受 它折磨着我
And that killed me. That crushed me.
你彻底征服我了
You completely won me over.
但这并不是我本意 我不想再让你回来的
You know I wasn't actually trying to win you over.
我只是想告诉你滚
I was trying to tell you to fuck off.
而且我也已经说过了
And I had.
然后现在你又回来
And now, you've come back and...
你开始回忆这一切
and you've opened the whole thing up again.
而且我觉得其实 我想我得走了
And I think actually, I think I'm gonna have to go.
拿着吧
Take that.
我要走了 这一切有点太...
I'm gonna go 'cause it's all a bit much.
我明白你的感受
I hear you.
- 你慢慢调整 我哪都不会去的 - 什么?你要一直坐在这把椅子吗?
- Take your time. I'm not going anywhere. - What? Are you gonna stay on the bench?
是的 我会留下来的 我要永远活在这把椅子上
Yes. I'm gonna stay.I'm gonna live on this bench.
周六到Gramercy来吧 拜托了
Come to The Gramercy. On Saturday. Please.
听听这首歌
Just hear the song.
我希望你能看到人们有多喜欢
I want you to see how everyone's just falling in love
喜欢这首你所写的东西
with what you created.
那请不要以那种方式唱
Please don't play it like that.
好吧
Okay.
哇 看看你 这么优雅 这才是我女儿
Well, look at you. A vision of pure class. There's my daughter.
- 不是吧 就是这张吗? - 是啊
- No way. Is this it? - Yeah.
- 就是这样 - 是的 - 你看起来棒极了
- There you are. - Yeah. - You look great.
我能拿去给我的小伙伴们看么?
Can I keep this? Show all my friends?
这就是它存在的意义呀
That's what it's for, babe.
看看你
Look at you.
太好笑了
Hilarious.
有什么好笑的?
Why is that hilarious?
只是我竟然一直不知道你这么有才华 我竟然不知道
I just had no idea you were that talented. I mean, I just didn't know.
你是一个真正的吉他手 说真的你很有天赋
You’re a real guitar player. You got some talent. Seriously.
然后呢?你想要让我组个乐队?
What? Do you want me to start a band now?
是啊!那就组乐队吧!
Yeah! Let's start a band!
好啊 组乐队吧!
Let's start a band！
为什么不呢?我会帮你录歌 当你的制作人
Yeah, Why not? I'll record you. I'll produce you.
- 我觉得这很不错啊 - 是吗? - 是啊
- I like this idea. - Do you? - Yeah.
你会支持么?
You all motivated now?
- 是啊 这就是一个家族企业 像杰克逊五兄弟一样 - 到了
- It's a family business. It's like the Jackson Five. - There you go.
- 穆里根一家 - 你进来吗?
- The Mulligan Three. - You coming in?
不了 我还要把片子放给索尔听 看看能不能达成协议
No. I'm going to go play that for Saul and see if we can get a deal.
祝你好运 记得告诉我情况
Good luck. Let me know how it goes.
我爱你
I love you.
我知道
I know you do.
来吧 对 就是这样 太漂亮了
Come on. Yeah. So pretty.
再见!
Bye!
谢谢你们的到来
Thanks for coming in guys.
这确实很棒 是一张很伟大的专辑
This is fantastic. You've got a great record.
我第一次没用心听 但是我不想再错过了
I missed it on the first listen. But I don't want to miss it again.
我们很高兴你喜欢它
We're very glad that you like it.
我已经联系了几个洛杉矶的工作室
Well, I reached out to some of my studio connects in L.A.
然后我们觉得可以放到电影里
and I was thinking we could get the first track placed in a film.
出部电影 这也是一种推销策略
Write a film. There's also pilot season right now.
是吗 老兄 但我们对这些不感兴趣
Yeah man, we're not interested in any of that stuff.
好吧 那么
Okay, so then
你想怎么样?我们这是在谈论什么?
What are you interested in? What are we doing here?
我觉得首先Dan应该回来工作
Well, I think Dan needs his job back.
是的 当然 说什么呢? 用我的办公室吧 我不介意的
Yeah, sure. What? Take my office. I don't care.
好吧 我想知道该怎么处理这张专辑?
Okay. I guess I want to know, how does this work?
我们发行了一张专辑 我们一张卖...
We put the album out. We sell it for...
就说每张专辑十块钱吧
Let's say an album costs ten dollars a unit.
音乐人赚取一美元
The artist gets a dollar.
就跟卖书是一样的
It's the same in publishing. It's a buck for a book.
好吧 我在用一种特殊的方式想这个问题
Oh, I'm just thinking for this specifically.
我要组织一下语言
I have to get my head around it.
我们做了一张不花任何成本的这张专辑
The album doesn't have any overhead because we did it.
这样子分配的话...
And then, distribution...
它不会在店外的任何地方出售 它将被放到网上
It's not gonna go in stores. It's gonna go online.
我们将有什么?有了口碑?
And publicity would be...What? Word of mouth?
所以 我认为我不明白的是...
So, I think what I'm wondering is...
你为什么拿走我剩余的九美元?
why do you get nine out of ten of my dollars?
Gretta 你真是一个聪明的姑娘
Gretta, you're a very smart young woman.
你也是一个很坚定的艺术家
And you're a determined artist.
你有张这么好的专辑
You have a wonderful project here.
而且 你的身后也会有两个团队指导你 推动你向正确的方向走
And with the right team behind you to push you and guide you to the right direction.
或者再聘请几位厉害的制作人替你再录几首歌
Maybe hire a hot-shot producer to remix a couple tracks.
这将给你漫长的职业生涯创造一个顶点
You could have a hit record and a very long career.
但是你知道 最终一切都取决于你
But you know, ultimately that's up to you.
- 你完全控制住他们了 - 我知道
- Ah, you had them. You wound him up. - I know.
当你没那么用心时最终的目标却总会实现 这真是太有趣了
It's amazing when you're not actually that interested, you always win the hand.
是嘛 对我来说 事情从来没有这样过
Yeah. That's never really worked out that well for me.
我倒经常这样
I found it worked very well.
你会拿下那份合同的 那混蛋肯定会给你提供合同的
You're gonna get a deal. That asshole is gonna give you a deal.
- 不过到时候你就得谦虚一点了 - 绝不 - 当然了
- You might have to compromise a little bit. - Never. - Of course.
- 我们应该经常这样做 - 你是什么意思?
Hey, we should do a bunch of these. - What do you mean?
- 你喜欢欧版不? - 我喜欢啊
- Do you like the European Series? - I like that.
巴黎磁带 布拉格会议
The Paris Tapes. The Prague Sessions.
柏林录音
The Berlin Recordings.
我们可以坐火车在欧洲旅行
We could go all over Europe by rail.
带着全组的人去
We could take the whole gang
Rachel Malcolm Steve
Rachel, Malcolm, Steve.
- 所以... - 所以...
- So... - So...
好吧 我想只能过段时间再见啦
Oh look. I guess I'll see you in a while.
谢谢
Thank you.
来表演吧 你的名字已经在演出列表上了 拜托了 Dave
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
谢谢
Thank you.
换吉他
Guitar change.
下一首歌曲实际上是一个很棒的音乐人送我的礼物
This next song was actually given to me by an amazing songwriter
更重要的是 她一个很棒的女人
and an even more amazing woman.
所以这是一个很特别的歌
So it's a very special song.
我们要唱她的这首歌
We're gonna do her arrangement of it.
如果她在这里 我不知道她是否会来
So If she's here. I'm not sure that she is.
但我真希望她在这里可以一起来表演这首歌
I'd love for her to come up and join us on this one.
吉他就在放在这里 所以
There's a guitar right there, so
如果你在这里 就上来加入我们吧
If you're here, please join us.
对我来说 这真的是一首很特别的歌
It's a really special song to me.
以你的方式来演唱
See your vision of this song through.
Lost Stars - Adam Levine
这只不过是
Please don't see
一个小男孩坐观空仰梦幻
Just a boy caught up in dreams and fantasies
我要用心
Please see me
触碰身边的意中人
reaching out for someone I can't see
牵起我的手吧
Take my hand
看看明天我们会梦醒何处
Let's see where we wake up tomorrow
也别再计划了
Best laid plans
等待一夜就知心属
Sometimes are just a one night stand
就让丘比特 收回那犹豫不决的箭吧
I'll be damned cupid's demanding back his arrow
就让我们饮醉在那压抑的泪水中吧
So let's get drunk on our tears
上帝请告诉我们
And god, tell us the reason
年轻并非是虚度青春的理由
Youth is wasted on the young
又到了这追逐的季节
It's hunting season
羔羊们都在纵情跳跃
and the lambs are on the run
找寻着生命的意义
searching for meaning
若夜空中星辰不再相互凝望闪烁
But are we all lost stars
将如何继续照亮这黑暗
trying to light up the dark?
我们是谁?
Who are we?
只不过是沧海一栗的尘埃
Just a speck of dust within the galaxy
我哀嚎着
Woe is me
如若不小心我们变成了现实
if we're not careful turns into reality
但你还敢记起
But don't you dare let our best memories
这带给你的伤痛回忆吗
bring you sorrow?
昨天我看见了一只雄狮亲吻了一只麋鹿
Yesterday I saw a lion kiss a deer
再翻一页
Turn the page
或许我们会发现一个全新的结局
maybe we'll find a brand new ending
我们将在哪里伴着泪水翩翩起舞
where we're dancing in our tears
上帝请告诉我们
And god tell us the reason
年轻并非是虚度青春的理由
youth is wasted on the young
又到了这追逐的季节
It's hunting season
羔羊们都在纵情跳跃
and the lambs are on the run
找寻着生命的意义
searching for meaning
若夜空中星辰不再相互凝望闪烁
But are we all lost stars
将如何继续照亮黑暗?
trying to light up the dark?
我想我是看见你哭了
And I thought I saw you out there crying
我想我听到了你呼唤着我的名字
and I thought I heard you call my name
我想我是看见你哭了
and I thought I heard you out there crying
还是一成不变
just the same
上帝请告诉我们
God, give us the reason
年轻并非是虚度青春的理由
Youth is wasted on the young
又到了这追逐的季节
It's hunting season
羔羊们都在纵情跳跃
and this lamb is on the run
找寻着生命的意义
searching for meaning
若夜空中星辰不再相互凝望闪烁
But are we all lost stars
将如何继续照亮黑暗
trying to light up the dark?
我想我是看见你哭了
And I thought I saw you out there crying
我想我听到了你呼唤着我的名字
and I thought I heard you call my name
我想我是看见你哭了
and I thought I heard you out there crying
若夜空中星辰不再相互凝望闪烁
But are we all lost stars
将如何继续照亮黑暗?
trying to light up the dark?
若夜空中星辰不再相互凝望闪烁
But are we all lost stars
将如何继续照亮黑暗?
trying to light up the dark?
献给我的兄弟Jim
(未完)
- 嘿 - 嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
你要去哪里?
Where are you going?
回家
Home.
你脑子进水啦?
What's on your mind?
我不想让你公司发行这张专辑了
I don't want your label to release my album.
- 好吧 - 可以?真的吗?
- Fine. - Fine? Really?
不 我还以为你一定会很难过的
No, because I thought that you'd be really upset.
不会 这是你的专辑
No, it's your album.
- 所以 你想用它做什么呢? - 好啦
- So, what do you want to do with it then? - There it is.
一美元一整张专辑 一美元一本书
That's the whole album for a dollar. A buck for a book.
这一切的故事 一旦你这样做了 就只能这样了 就结束了
The whole thing. Now, once this goes out, that's it. They're gone.
- 是的 - 你确定要这么做? - 是的 两美元怎么样?
- Yeah. - Are you sure you want to do this? - Yeah. How about two bucks?
真是资本主义家 不要 一美元就好
Such a capitalist. No, a buck is fair.
然后 我们一群人再平分
And then we'll split it evenly between everyone
Malcolm Rachel 还有大家 快点!
Malcolm Rachel and everyone. Come on!
我一按下去就结束了哦
Once I press this, that's it.
我在向我的事业开战
I'm going to war with my whole business.
太刺激啦
That's so exciting.
你在做什么呢?
What are you doing?
呼叫援助
Calling reinforcements.
哇 看看这 我让他发个微博
Check it out. I got Troublegum to tweet out the album.
他有多少粉丝?
How many followers does he have?
几乎全世界
Apparently the entire world.
活着的人们
Just about every living human being.
- Mulligan先生 - 早安 - 早安
- Mr. Mulligan. - Good morning. - Good morning.
网上有条关于你的消息
News for you on the inter webs.
卧槽!
Shit!
- 你不知道这事? - No. - No?
- You didn’t know nothing about this? - 不知道 - 不知道吗?
她已经卖出了多少?
How many did she sell?
近万份 就今天
Ten thousand. Today.
Troublegum还发微博了呢
Troublegum tweeted about it.
如果Troublegum帮助她 那是因为他喜欢她
If Troublegum helped her out, it's because he liked her.
他们都是艺术家
They're artists.
- 你确定你对这事儿完全不知情? - 完全不知情
- You didn't know nothing about this? - Nothing.
- 还挺好笑的 - 真的吗?
- Kind of funny though. - Is it really?
还真是有趣呢
It's pretty funny, man.
哇 你真的知道如何选择了
Boo-boo, you know how to pick them.
这也很不错嘛
It's kind of good.
是的 就是有点不知道天高地厚
Sure is. Kind of uppity.
收拾收拾你可以走了
Clean out your locker.
待会儿见
See you later.
感谢观看
翻译/时间轴/校对:@嘉鱼鱼鱼鱼鱼鱼